Aneta Stojanowska

Senior product designer & Webflow expert, Rotterdam NL

SUMMARY

I translate static pdf's into highly visual and interactive content. From white papers, annual reports and graphs into branded infographics, visual statistics, interactive timelines and reviews. I offer a full service from UX research to data processing and from design to technology. Simple, converting and in entertaining fashion.

CONTACT

- anetastojanowska.nl
- □ +31 6 4094 9324
- @ hi@anetastojanowska.nl
- in linkedin.com/astojanowska

SELECTED WORK

TOPS Personeel

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022 | Rotterdam

Translating data from TOPS' employee satisfaction survey into a visual, engaging en personalised infographic.

https://www.anetastojanowska.nl/ #project-one

Aegon

Jun 2021 - Nov 2021 | Den Haag Improvement of an interactive calculation tool for a pension platform to request quotes, test knowledge and show insight.

https://www.anetastojanowska.nl/
#project-two

Matchcare

Nov 2020 - May 2021 | Nieuwegein
Creating data discovery experience through
translating complex data into clear,
scannable and relevant data visualisation.

https://www.anetastojanowska.nl/
#project-three

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

Freelancer

Jun 2021 - Present / Rotterdam & remote

Designing and developing an interactive landing pages that is reusable and shareable.

BI Consultant

UWV

Jan 2018 - Jan 2020 | Amsterdam

Developing and designing interactive BI data visualizations with maximum data-ink ratio.

SKILLS

Interaction Design
Typography
Design System
Usability Testing
HTML/CSS

Product Designer

Govin

Jan 2022 - Mar 2022 / Amsterdam

Designing a responsive investment platform for ESG investors where shareholders can view reporting dashboards.

Graphic Designer

DOOR!, De Wilde Bühne, You Enter Sep 2016 - Jan 2018 | Amsterdam

Creating and designing online marketing and social media campaigns, newsletters and interactive media such as (website) banners.

TOOLS

Figma Webflow Maze

LANGUAGES

Dutch (fluent)
English (fluent)
Polish (native)

EDUCATION

Business & Data Analytics

Hogeschool van Amsterdam Jan 2018 - Jan 2020

International Business & Mgnt

Hogeschool Inholland, Diemen Sep 2003 - May 2007

HOBBIES

DJ'en Badminton Reading books Painting